<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<root>

  <level1>

    <intro>

      Good evening worker 2-5-9-4, I'am Argos, the AI assigned to help you with your new job at this work unit. We're currently installing a neural
      implant that will help you focus on your job here at the council for peace and prosperity. Side effects include, nausia, shortness of breath,
      stomach pain, cramps, temporary color blindness, fainting, myocardial infarction, and seizures.

      Upon completion of the installation, I will begin your introduction
      which will aquant you with the council for peace and prosperity, your work unit, and what you will be doing here. Please remain still while the installation completes.
      
      The council for peace and prosparity, of which this embol reprosents, was foraged in the aftermath of a world in conflict.
      People from all around the world fought each other everyday, everywhere on the planet. This erupted to extreme heights
      when nuclear missels began to detonate around the planet. Most of the worlds population was atomized, and those who
      surivied faced a slow death of radiation posioning. This is well know to you, and no doubt everyone who lives within
      the protective walls and shields of Varlin. What is less know is the creation of the council for peace and prosperity,
      something far less expressed to the impovereshed variables who roam the streets, clinging to whats left of the
      old world. The council for prosperity and peace arose in the power vaccume created when the worlds governments fell.
      The council is home to those who created the walls, and powerful shields atop Varlin, great engineers, as well as entreprenuers
      who funded the projects have their part aswell. The council keeps order, no conflict has ever occured within
      Varlin since its founding 54 years ago.
      
      Your work unit is one of many that perform the various important tasks that uphold the councils control, and ability
      to keep the populace safe. The many offices and tall buildings keep workers such as your self far away from the 
      shuffiling people of the streets, and the implant keeps workers producing at maximum efficentcy. Workers like you 
      are the backbone of the council, dedicated and loyal, unlike the variables who lack an implant. It's up to you to
      keep them safe from themselves, that is what you will do here.
      
      The computer infront of you will be how you complete various taks handed down to you from the council, like how I
      was tasked to assist you. When you are ready, log in to your computer, and we will begin your training.

    </intro>
    
  </level1>
  
  
  
  
  
</root>